Warning: Crazy People are coming.
Crazy People is a comedy, romance film directed by Tony Bill.
A bitter ad executive, who has reached his breaking point, finds himself in a mental institution,
where his career actually begins to thrive with the help of the hospital's patients.
Emory Leeson, played by Dudley Moore.
Kathy Burgess, played by Daryl Hannah.
Stephen Bachman, played by Paul Reiser.
Drucker, played by J. T. Walsh.
Bruce, played by Bill Smitrovich.
Judge, played by Alan North.
Crazy People is a 1990 American black comedy film starring Dudley Moore and
Daryl Hannah, directed by Tony Bill, and music by Cliff Eidelman.
The film explores themes of advertising, mental illness,
advertising executive, advertising agency.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.